[Christian Child Sponsorship - Compassion - Child Charity Organization](https://www.compassion.com/)

1. [Gift Catalog](https://www.compassion.com/charitable-gift-catalog.htm)
2. [My Account](https://www.compassion.com/my-account/summary.htm) [(log in)](https://www.compassion.com/account/login.htm)
    
    #### Log in
    
    * Username 
    * Password Your password is hidden. 
    * [ ]  Remember me
    * 
        
        First time logging in?  

3. [Checkout (0)](https://www.compassion.com/checkout/checkout-cart.htm)
    
    #### Summary
    
    0 items
    
    ##### Added Recently

4. [Contact Us](https://www.compassion.com/contact/)
5. Search text field 

    1. [View All Children](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/view-all-children.htm)
    2. [View Longest Waiting Children](https://www.compassion.com/child-sponsorship/waiting-child.htm?LongestWaitingFilter=180)
    3. [Search for a Child](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/search_for_a_child_to_sponsor.htm)
    4. [Select a Child For Me](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/select-a-child-for-me.htm)
    5. [What Is Child Sponsorship?](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/what-is-child-sponsorship/)
    6. [Why Sponsor a Child?](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/how-child-sponsorship-helps.htm)
    7. [How to Sponsor a Child](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/how-to-sponsor-a-child.htm)
    8. [Child Sponsorship FAQ](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/sponsorship-faq.htm)
    9. [Child Sponsorship Reviews](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/sponsor_a_child_reviews.htm)
    10. [Financial Integrity](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/child-sponsorship-trustworthy-charity.htm)
    
    ##### It's My Birthday!
    
    Choose Me

    1. [Donate to a Cause](https://www.compassion.com/ways-to-donate.htm)
    2. [Meet Critical Needs](https://www.compassion.com/where-most-needed.htm)
    3. [Shop Our Gift Catalog](https://www.compassion.com/charitable-gift-catalog.htm)
    4. [Match Your Gift](https://www.compassion.com/donate/matching-gifts.htm)
    5. [Other Ways to Give](https://www.compassion.com/donate/other-ways-to-give.htm)
    
    ##### Give Where It's Most Needed
    
    Homelessness. Medical emergencies. Natural disaster. Your donation helps children when they need it most..

    1. [Donate](https://www.compassion.com/ways-to-donate.htm)
    2. [Volunteer](https://www.compassion.com/volunteer/join-volunteer-network.htm)
    3. [Pray](https://www.compassion.com/prayer.htm)
    4. [Write Your Child](https://www.compassion.com/letter-writing/write-my-child.htm)
    5. [Visit Your Child](https://www.compassion.com/get-involved/trips-visits.htm)
    
    1. [Compassion Sunday](https://www.compassion.com/compassionsunday/)
    2. [Churches](https://www.compassion.com/church-engagement/)
    3. [Businesses](https://www.compassion.com/corporate-partners/corporate-partners.htm)
    4. [Speakers and Artists](https://www.compassion.com/christian-speakers/christian-speakers-artists.htm)
    5. [Events and Festivals](https://www.compassion.com/get-involved/event-sponsorship.htm)
    6. [Pro Athletes](https://www.compassion.com/athletes/athletes.htm)

    1. [What Makes Us Distinct](https://www.compassion.com/about/what-makes-us-distinct.htm)
    2. [Who We Are](https://www.compassion.com/about/what-is-compassion.htm)
    3. [What We Do](https://www.compassion.com/child-development-model.htm)
    4. [Where We Work](https://www.compassion.com/where-we-work.htm)
    5. [Press Center](https://www.compassion.com/press-center.htm)
    6. [Financial Integrity](https://www.compassion.com/about/financial.htm)
    7. [Accountability Report](https://www.compassion.com/about/accountability-report.htm)
    8. [Careers](https://www.compassion.com/employment/christian-employment.htm)
    9. [FAQ](https://www.compassion.com/about/faq.htm)

    1. [Write](https://www.compassion.com/for-sponsors/write.htm)
    2. [Give](https://www.compassion.com/for-sponsors/give.htm)
    3. [Pray](https://www.compassion.com/for-sponsors/pray.htm)
    4. [Visit](https://www.compassion.com/get-involved/trips-visits.htm)
    5. [Crisis Updates](https://www.compassion.com/where-we-work/crisis-updates.htm)
    6. [More Resources](https://www.compassion.com/for-sponsors/resources/default.htm)

Menu

Search text fields 

1. [Sponsor a Child\>](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/default.htm)

    ##### Sponsor a Child
    
    1. [View All Children](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/view-all-children.htm)
    2. [View Longest Waiting Children](https://www.compassion.com/child-sponsorship/waiting-child.htm?LongestWaitingFilter=180)
    3. [Search for a Child](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/search_for_a_child_to_sponsor.htm)
    4. [Select a Child For Me](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/select-a-child-for-me.htm)
    5. [What Is Child Sponsorship?](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/what-is-child-sponsorship/)
    6. [Why Sponsor a Child?](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/how-child-sponsorship-helps.htm)
    7. [How to Sponsor a Child](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/how-to-sponsor-a-child.htm)
    8. [Child Sponsorship FAQ](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/sponsorship-faq.htm)
    9. [Child Sponsorship Reviews](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/sponsor_a_child_reviews.htm)
    10. [Financial Integrity](https://www.compassion.com/sponsor_a_child/child-sponsorship-trustworthy-charity.htm)
    
2. [Ways to Donate\>](https://www.compassion.com/ways-to-donate.htm)

    ##### Ways to Donate
    
    1. [Donate to a Cause](https://www.compassion.com/ways-to-donate.htm)
    2. [Meet Critical Needs](https://www.compassion.com/where-most-needed.htm)
    3. [Shop Our Gift Catalog](https://www.compassion.com/charitable-gift-catalog.htm)
    4. [Match Your Gift](https://www.compassion.com/donate/matching-gifts.htm)
    5. [Other Ways to Give](https://www.compassion.com/donate/other-ways-to-give.htm)
    
3. [Get Involved\>](https://www.compassion.com/get-involved.htm)

    ##### Get Involved
    
    1. [Donate](https://www.compassion.com/ways-to-donate.htm)
    2. [Fundraise](https://www.compassion.com/get-involved.htm)
    3. [Volunteer](https://www.compassion.com/volunteer/join-volunteer-network.htm)
    4. [Family Activity Ideas](https://www.compassion.com/sponsordonor/free-family-activities.htm)
    5. [Pray](https://www.compassion.com/prayer.htm)
    6. [Write Your Child](https://www.compassion.com/letter-writing/write-my-child.htm)
    7. [Visit Your Child](https://www.compassion.com/get-involved/trips-visits.htm)
    8. [Compassion Store](https://store.compassion.com/)
    9. [Pro Athletes](https://www.compassion.com/athletes/athletes.htm)
    
4. [About Us\>](https://www.compassion.com/about/about-us.htm)

    ##### About Us
    
    1. [What Makes Us Distinct](https://www.compassion.com/about/what-makes-us-distinct.htm)
    2. [Who We Are](https://www.compassion.com/about/what-is-compassion.htm)
    3. [What We Do](https://www.compassion.com/child-development-model.htm)
    4. [Where We Work](https://www.compassion.com/where-we-work.htm)
    5. [Press Center](https://www.compassion.com/press-center.htm)
    6. [Financial Integrity](https://www.compassion.com/about/financial.htm)
    7. [Accountability Report](https://www.compassion.com/about/accountability-report.htm)
    8. [Careers](https://www.compassion.com/employment/christian-employment.htm)
    9. [Tour Our Ministry Center](https://www.compassion.com/tours/colorado-springs-tours.htm)
    10. [FAQ](https://www.compassion.com/about/faq.htm)
    11. [Accountability Report](https://www.compassion.com/about/accountability-report.htm)
    
5. [For Sponsors\>](https://www.compassion.com/for-sponsors/default.htm)

    ##### For Sponsors
    
    1. [Write](https://www.compassion.com/for-sponsors/write.htm)
    2. [Give](https://www.compassion.com/for-sponsors/give.htm)
    3. [Pray](https://www.compassion.com/for-sponsors/pray.htm)
    4. [Visit](https://www.compassion.com/get-involved/trips-visits.htm)
    5. [Crisis Updates](https://www.compassion.com/where-we-work/crisis-updates.htm)
    6. [More Resources](https://www.compassion.com/for-sponsors/resources/default.htm)
    
6. [Donate Now](https://www.compassion.com/donate.htm)
7. [Gift Catalog](https://www.compassion.com/charitable-gift-catalog.htm)
8. [Compassion Store](https://store.compassion.com/)
9. [My Account](https://www.compassion.com/my-account/summary.htm)
10. [My Cart](https://www.compassion.com/my-cart/checkout-information.htm)

1. [](https://www.compassion.com/ "Home")

3. Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

_Last revised: 12/22/2023_

### Our Commitment

Compassion International is committed to your privacy. We value your trust and want to assure you that we will always strive to be responsible in our management of your personal information.

We provide this Privacy Policy to make you aware of our privacy practices, and to inform you about the way your information is collected and used. We commit that any activity we engage in with your information is ultimately for the greater purpose of helping to release children from poverty in Jesus’ name.

If you have questions or concerns, please contact us at [(800) 336-7676](tel:800-336-7676 "call Compassion today"), Monday through Friday, 7 a.m. to 5:30 p.m. MT or [via email](https://www.compassion.com/contact/).

To learn more about our commitment to protecting the privacy of children in our program visit [https://www.compassion.com/how-we-work/commitment-child-protection.htm](https://www.compassion.com/how-we-work/commitment-child-protection.htm).

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how Compassion International (collectively, “Compassion,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) collects, uses, shares, and safeguards personal information. This Privacy Policy also tells you about your choices with respect to your personal information, and how you can reach us to get answers to your questions. You can jump to particular topics by going to the headings below:

#### Types of Information We Collect

The following provides examples of the types of information that we collect about you and how we use that information. It also indicates whether we share certain information we collect with third parties for purposes of targeted advertising.

**Types of Personal Information**

We collect your name and contact information when you create an account. We also collect information relating to the actions that you perform while logged into your account.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We use the personal information for our legitimate interest to better serve you to provide account related functionalities to our users. Accounts can be used for easy checkout and to save your preferences and transaction history.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **No**_

**Types of Personal Information**

We use cookies and similar technologies when you interact with our website. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website sends to a computer’s hard drive while a web site is viewed. See the [Cookies Section](#cookies-and-technology) below for more information.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We use these cookies for our legitimate interest to make our website operate efficiently. We may also use cookies to troubleshoot user issues and to learn how you use our website as well as to optimize your experience. Where required by law, we base the use of non-essential cookies upon consent.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **Yes**_

**Types of Personal Information**

We may place tracking technology on our website that collects analytics, records how you interact with our website, or allows us to participate in behavior-based advertising (or “targeted advertising”). This means that a third party uses technology (e.g., a cookie) to collect information about your use of our website so that they can report analytics to us or provide advertising about products and services tailored to your interests. That third party might also collect information over time and across different websites in order to serve advertisements on our website or other websites. Additionally, we may monitor and analyze your activity on our websites to improve your experience, which may include the use of third-party session replay software or services. See the [Cookies and Similar Technology Section](#cookies-and-technology) below for more information.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We use these cookies to engage in advertising and capture website analytics for our legitimate interest. Where required by law, we base the use of third-party cookies upon consent.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **Yes**_

[Donation and Sponsorship Information, including demographic information](#)

**Types of Personal Information**

We collect information from our donors and sponsors such as contact and payment information, and demographic information about our donors.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We use contact and payment information to process donations and sponsorships. We also use this information for our legitimate interest in updating you about your sponsorship or sponsored child. We also may alert you to other ways to engage with our ministry including giving opportunities and job opportunities. Occasionally we use other information including information from 3rd parties to learn about donors and sponsors for the purpose of identifying other individuals who might be interested in helping children in poverty. This includes sharing anonymized data with cooperative database providers.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **No**_

[Donor Advised Fund Information, Donor Life Income Agreement information, Wills and Estate Planning Information](#)

**Types of Personal Information**

We may collect your Social Security Number, birthdate, Driver’s License or other form of identification, bank account information along with Donor and Beneficiary Information.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We use this information to manage the donations that you make to Compassion.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **No**_

**Types of Personal Information**

If you receive email from us, we use certain tools to capture data related to when you open our message, click on any links it contains and make donations.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We use this information to understand how you interact with our communications for our legitimate interest and to better serve you.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **No**_

**Types of Personal Information**

If you apply for a job posting, or become an employee, we collect information necessary to process your application or to retain you as an employee. This may include, among other things, your Social Security Number. Providing this information is required for employment. We may also conduct behavioral testing to evaluate suitability for positions and this your responses may include some personal data.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We use information about job applicants in anticipation of employment and current employees to perform our obligations to employees and for compliance with employment law and other statutory requirements. We also use your information to have efficient staffing and work force operations in our legitimate interest.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **No**_

**Types of Personal Information**

If you travel on a Compassion Tour or participate in a Compassion event, including virtual events, with your acknowledgment we collect additional information about you including dietary preferences, health requirements, passport and visa information, background information, (including government identification numbers such as Social Security Number), video recordings, as well as emergency contact information.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We use this information for your safety and for the safety of children and to facilitate your participation in the event or tour for our legitimate interest.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **No**_

**Types of Personal Information**

If you provide us feedback or contact us for support, we will collect your name and e-mail address, as well as any other content that you send to us, in order to reply.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We have a legitimate interest in receiving, and acting upon, your feedback or issues.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **No**_

[Letters (and other communication) to Sponsored Children, including Photographs](#)

**Types of Personal Information**

If you write a letter to a sponsored child, we store those letters digitally including any information you include in the letter.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We store letters and communication for our legitimate interests, for example so that they can be referenced by both the writer and the child, as well as to monitor communications for inappropriate behavior. Other legitimate interests may include improving our services and/or informing you of opportunities to partner with Compassion based on letter content.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **No**_

**Types of Personal Information**

When you sign up for one of our mailing lists, we collect your email address or postal address.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We use your address to share information about our products and services with you and for our legitimate interest. Where required by law, we will obtain your consent to send promotional messages.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **Yes**_

**Types of Personal Information**

We may collect information that you provide as part of a co-branded promotion with one of our partners. If the partner will also use that information, a separate privacy notice will be provided at the time of collection that describes their use of the data.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We use your information for our legitimate interest to fulfill our promotions. We also use your information to support the legitimate interests of partners that we have disclosed.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **No**_

**Types of Personal Information**

We may collect information in these categories when you participate in research activities or as a consequence of Compassion being a religious organization. We may derive associated information from your participation in an event.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

This information is processed with your express consent. These types of information may be anonymized when possible. We collect this information to optimize our services.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **No**_

**Types of Personal Information**

When you participate in a survey or a research study, we collect information that you provide through the survey or questionnaires. If the survey or research is facilitated by a third-party service provider, the third party’s privacy policy applies to the collection, use, and disclosure of your information.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We have a legitimate interest in understanding your opinions and collecting information relevant to our organization.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **No**_

**Types of Personal Information**

When you participate in a sweepstakes or contest, we collect information about you which includes contact information to notify you if you are selected.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We have a legitimate interest in operating the sweepstakes. In some contexts, we are also required by law to collect information about those that enter into our sweepstakes, and we have a legitimate interest in complying with those laws.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **No**_

**Types of Personal Information**

Information relating to or needed to complete non-fungible token (NFT) purchases or sales, which may include transactional details, fees, and sales prices.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We use transactional information to complete NFT transactions and complete the contract that is entered into in the sale.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **No**_

**Types of Personal Information**

We use technology to monitor and record how you interact with our website. This includes which links you click on, pages you visit, actions you take, videos you watch or forms you complete. This also includes information about your device or browser.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We use this information to understand how you interact with our website to improve it, and to understand your preferences and interests in order to select offerings. We also use it to detect and prevent fraud. These are all our legitimate interests. We may share this information with third parties to facilitate these activities.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **No**_

**Types of Personal Information**

We collect information, including your browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to a computer when the Internet is used), domain name, click-activity, referring website, and/or a date/time stamp for visitors.

**Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We use this information to monitor our networks and the visitors to our websites. Among other things, it helps us understand which of our services is the most popular. These are all legitimate interests of Compassion.

_Is Personal Information Shared for Targeted Advertising? **No**_

Please note, if you fail to provide certain personal information when requested, we may not be able to complete certain transactions or perform obligations that we have to you (such as processing donations or sponsorships or facilitating your participation in the event or tour.)

In addition to the information that we collect from you directly, we also receive information about you from other sources, including third parties, business partners, our affiliates, or publicly available sources. For example, if you submit a job application, or become an employee, we conduct a background check. We also check the National Sex Offender registry to ensure the safety of Compassion’s sponsored children and use other public information to investigate possible sex offenses. We may verify the accuracy of your data by comparing it to 3rd party sources. We perform these checks to protect all the children that we serve and to serve with integrity.

We may also use personal information we acquire about you from 3rd party sources to help provide better service to you and to identify potential new supporters. One example of this would be comparing your address data to the National Change of Address service.

To learn more about our commitment to protecting the privacy of children in our program, visit [https://www.compassion.com/how-we-work/commitment-child-protection.htm.](https://www.compassion.com/how-we-work/commitment-child-protection.htm "Commitment to Child Protection")

#### Use and Processing of Information

In addition to the purposes and uses described above, we use information in the following ways:

* To identify you when you visit our website.
* To process donations and sponsorship.
* To improve our services and support our mission.
* To conduct analytics.
* To respond to inquiries related to support, employment opportunities, or other requests.
* To send marketing and promotional materials, including information relating to Compassion’s mission and programs.
* In order to update you on your sponsored child and special events.
* To create and steward effective partnerships with churches and volunteers.
* For internal administrative purposes, as well as to manage our relationships.

Although the sections above describe our primary purpose in collecting your information, in many situations we have more than one purpose. As a result, our collection and processing of your information is based in different contexts upon your consent, our need to perform a contract, our obligations under law, and/or Compassion’s legitimate interest.

To the extent we maintain and use personal information in a deidentified form, we will not attempt to reidentify the information, except for the purpose of determining whether our deidentification processes satisfy our legal obligations.

#### Sharing of Information

We may disclose information to third parties, including service providers, partners, individuals and other third parties, for various reasons. The table below describes the categories of personal information we collect and the categories of third parties to whom we disclose such personal information. We do not sell your personal information, nor do we participate in any sharing that would constitute a sale under applicable law.

**Category of Personal Information**

Contact information – such as your first and last name, postal address, email address, and phone number.

**Category of Recipients**

* Data analytics providers
* Marketing service providers
* Communications providers
* Partners
* Payment processors
* Social media platforms

**Category of Personal Information**

Other identifiers – such as IP address or other online identifiers.

**Category of Recipients**

* Data analytics providers

**Category of Personal Information**

Government Issued Identification – such as social security number, driver's license number, or state issued identification number, passport number.

**Category of Recipients**

* Payment processors
* Other Service Providers

**Category of Personal Information**

Financial Information – such as bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, and other financial information.

**Category of Recipients**

* Payment processors

**Category of Personal Information**

Demographic information – such as birthdate, age, gender, marital status, income, employment, language, family, and education.

**Category of Recipients**

* Data analytics providers
* Marketing service providers
* Communications providers

**Category of Personal Information**

Health Related Information about Participants and relevant health and safety information for travelers.

**Category of Recipients**

* Other Service Providers
* Partners

**Category of Personal Information**

Religious, Denominational, and Ethnicity based information

**Category of Recipients**

* Data analytics providers
* Other Service Providers
* Communications providers
* Partners

**Category of Personal Information**

Commercial information – such as information about products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.

**Category of Recipients**

* Data analytics providers
* Other Service Providers
* Payment processors
* Professional services organizations, this may include auditors and law firms

**Category of Personal Information**

Internet or other electronic network activity information – this may include browsing history, search history, and information regarding an individual’s interaction with an internet website, application, or advertisement.

**Category of Recipients**

* Data analytics providers
* Internet service providers
* Operating systems and platforms
* Other Service Providers
* Social media platforms

**Category of Personal Information**

Geolocation data

**Category of Recipients**

* Data analytics providers
* Other Service Providers
* Communications providers
* Partners
* Social media platforms

**Category of Personal Information**

Inferences drawn from any of the information listed above

**Category of Recipients**

* Data analytics providers
* Other Service Providers
* Partners
* Social media platforms

In addition to the specific situations discussed above, we may disclose any of the categories of information listed above in the following situations:

1. **Affiliates.** We share information with Compassion affiliates (e.g., international Compassion entities).
2. **Other Disclosures with Your Consent.** We may disclose your information with third parties when we have your consent or direction to do so.
3. **Other Disclosures without Your Consent.** We disclose information in response to subpoenas, warrants, or court orders, or in connection with any legal process, or to comply with relevant laws. We may also share your information in order to establish or exercise our rights, to defend against a legal claim, to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding possible illegal activities, suspected fraud, safety of person or property, or a violation of our policies, or to comply with your request for the shipment of products by or the provision of services by a third-party intermediary.
4. **Public.** Some of our websites provide the opportunity to post comments, or reviews, in a public forum. If you decide to submit information on these pages, that information may be publicly available.
5. **Partners** We may engage in partnerships and joint ventures with third party organizations. In order to accomplish the purposes described in our use and processing of information that are in our legitimate interest, we may share your personal information with these organizations.

#### Cookies and Similar Technology

A cookie is a series of data characters that, when programmed into a website, is placed by the web server into the browser's application folder on your computer. Once placed onto your machine, the cookie will allow the website to "recognize" you as a unique individual. Cookies do not collect data from the end user's device.

Cookies are used to determine the success of Compassion's website and marketing campaigns. This allows us to be good stewards with the donations that are given to us to determine our online effectiveness, which also helps keep our expenses low.

Cookies can be removed from your device. Also, depending on what type of web browser and what browser version you are using, you may be able to change the properties on your cookie file so that cookies are not used or saved. Please check with your browser provider for more information on removing cookies.

In addition to cookies, we use other technologies, including pixel tags, to gather information on how visitors interact with our website and to help us efficiently monitor our website and marketing campaigns. These technologies, for example, show us popular pages, conversion rates, click-throughs and other information that can be used to improve our website. We also occasionally share select non-personal information with trusted third parties. Compassion and its third-party vendors use pixel tags to track and analyze non-personally-identifiable usage information to compile statistical traffic analysis or usage patterns. Third-party cookies may also be used to inform, optimize and serve Compassion ads on other websites based on your visits to Compassion websites.

We collect information on the pages you have visited on our Website and the contents of those pages, any information you input, your referring URL or IP address, your time of visit and related session information, your requested page, displayed and modified html, Web browser type, user agent, status of request (successful reply), cookies, browser timings, additional API/AJAX requests and responses, query string, mouse movements, page scrolls, clicks, device orientation when applicable, screen size, window size, selections, data entered, and information below. We may associate user identifiable information with the data collected so that we may better improve your experience. We also use this data to better understand Web site usage in the aggregate so that we know what areas of our Web site users prefer or we can improve. This information is stored and can be used for session replay as well as statistical reporting.

#### Your Rights and Choices

Compassion provides all rights to your information that are required by law. In any case, Compassion will consider all requests from individuals regarding their personal information. These requests may include:

1. **Access to Your Personal Information.** You may request access to your personal information or confirmation that we have information about you by contacting us at the address described below. In certain limited circumstances, you may also request to receive access to your data in a portable, machine-readable format. If required by law, upon request, we will grant you reasonable access to the personal information that we have about you.
2. **Changes to Your Personal Information.** We rely on you to update and correct your personal information. Our website allows you to modify your account profile. You may also contact us at the address described below in order to request that your information be modified. Note that we keep historical information in our backup files as permitted by law.
3. **Deletion of Your Personal Information.** You may request that we delete your personal information by contacting us at the address described below. If required by law we will grant a request to delete information, but you should note that in many situations we must keep your personal information to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements, or for another one of our business purposes
4. **Online Tracking.** We do not currently recognize "Do Not Track" instructions.
5. **Objection to or Restriction of Certain Processing.** In certain scenarios and in certain jurisdictions, you can object to our processing of your personal information, or request that we restrict processing of your personal information, by contacting us at the address described below.
6. **Promotional Emails.** You may choose to provide us with your email address for the purpose of allowing us to send materials to you. You can stop receiving promotional emails by following the unsubscribe instructions in e-mails that you receive. If you decide not to receive promotional emails, we will still send you service-related communications.
7. **Text Messages.** To discontinue SMS text messages from Compassion, text STOP to 97646. To learn more about SMS Terms and Conditions visit [https://www.compassion.com/sms-terms-and-conditions.htm](https://www.compassion.com/sms-terms-and-conditions.htm "SMS Terms and Conditions").
8. **Revocation of Consent.** You may revoke consent to processing (where such processing is based upon consent) by contacting us at the address described below. If you revoke your consent for the processing of personal information, then we may no longer be able to facilitate a child sponsorship for you or provide you with other services.
9. **Opt-out of Targeted Advertising.** You may opt-out of targeted advertising by contacting us at the address listed below. If you are a Colorado resident, you may have an authorized agent submit a request on your behalf by having them contact us at the address described below.

Please note, not all of the rights described above are absolute, and they do not apply in all circumstances. In some cases, we will limit or deny your request if the law permits or requires us to do so, or if we are unable to adequately verify your identity. We will not discriminate against individuals who exercise their privacy rights under applicable law.

Note that, as required by law, we will require you to prove your identity. We may verify your identity by phone call or email. Depending on your request, we will ask for information such as your name, address, phone number, account number and/or billing information. We may also ask you to provide a signed declaration confirming your identity.

If you disagree with our denial of a request, you may appeal our decision by contacting us as indicated in the "Contact Information" section below with the subject line "Appeal."

#### How We Protect and Retain Personal Information

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is fully secure. While we use reasonable efforts to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information. In the event that we are required by law to inform you of a breach to your personal information we will notify you electronically, in writing, or by telephone, if legally permitted.

Some of our websites permit you to create an account. When you do you will be prompted to create a password. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password, and you are responsible for any access to or use of your account by someone else that has obtained your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by you. You should notify us of any unauthorized use of your password or account.

We retain your personal information for only as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. To determine the appropriate retention period for personal information, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the information, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the information, the purposes for which we obtained the information and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, as well as applicable legal requirements.

#### Miscellaneous

The following additional information relates to our privacy practices:

* **Transmission of Information to Other Countries.** Your information may be processed in a foreign country where privacy laws are less stringent than the laws in your country. By submitting your personal information to us you agree to the transfer, storage, and processing of your information in a country other than your country of residence, including, but not necessarily limited to, the Unites States. Compassion utilizes Standard Contractual Clauses as an adequacy measure for data transfers from the European Union.
* **Third Party Applications/Websites.** We have no control over the privacy practices of websites or applications that we do not own. In order to complete certain kinds of NFT transactions you may need to use third-party applications. In doing so you may be required to provide personal data to such third-party applications and in those cases, the privacy policies and terms of the third party will apply to the processing.
* **Changes to This Privacy Policy.** We may change our privacy policy and practices over time. To the extent that our Privacy Policy changes in a material way, the policy that was in place at the time that you submitted personal information to us will generally govern that information unless we receive your consent to the new privacy policy. We will note the effective date of the latest version at the beginning of the Privacy Policy.

#### Contact Information

If you have any questions, comments, or complaints concerning our privacy practices or conditions of use, or if you need to access this Privacy Policy in an alternative format due to having a disability, please contact us at the appropriate address below. We will attempt to respond to your requests and to provide you with additional privacy-related information.

Compassion International  
12290 Voyager Parkway  
Colorado Springs, CO 80921

If you are not satisfied with our response and are in the European Union or the United Kingdom, you may have a right to lodge a complaint with your local supervisory authority.

If you have questions or want to exercise your data subject rights, or opt-out of targeted advertising, please contact our Data Protection Officer at [\[email protected\]](https://www.compassion.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

#### Children's Data

**Outside of our programs for children, we do not intentionally collect information about or from children.**

We do not intend to collect personal information from children under 18 who are not part of our program. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 18 has given us personal information, contact us at [(800) 336-7676](tel:800-336-7676 "call Compassion today"), Monday through Friday, 7 a.m. to 5:30 p.m. MT or [via email](https://www.compassion.com/contact/). Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children's privacy online [here](https://consumer.ftc.gov/identity-theft-and-online-security/protecting-kids-online).

**Effective Date: 12/22/2023**

Sponsor a Child Today

Showing results for ( children found):

* **Sort By:**
* Choose Priority Age (Youngest) Age (Oldest) Longest Waiting Birthday Today

Loading

* [Prev](#) Prev
* [1](#)1
* ...
* [](#)1
* ...
* [Next](#) Next

Showing – of children

24 per page 48 per page 72 per page

Sorry, there was a problem retrieving the children for this page. Please try again.

Sorry, there were no children found. Please use the search form to find a child to sponsor.

Similar Children:

Suggested Searches

Search for a Child to Sponsor

Where in The World No Preference Africa    Burkina Faso    Ethiopia    Ghana    Kenya    Rwanda    Tanzania    Togo    Uganda Asia    Bangladesh    Indonesia    Philippines    Sri Lanka    Thailand Central America and Caribbean    Dominican Republic    El Salvador    Guatemala    Haiti    Honduras    Mexico    Nicaragua South America    Bolivia    Brazil    Colombia    Ecuador    Peru

Gender No Preference Male Female

Age Range:  

Birthday [Select Today](#)

Month January February March April May June July August September October November December Day 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 30 31 Year 2023 2022 2021 2020 2019 2018 2017 2016 2015 2014 2013 2012 2011 2010 2009 2008 2007 2006 2005 2004 2003 2002

[Show more search options (child name, with disability and more)](#)

Longest Waiting No Preference Yes

Orphaned Child No Preference Yes

Vulnerable to Exploitation No Preference Yes

Affected by HIV/AIDS No Preference Yes

Children with Disabilities No Preference Yes

Child First Name 

Child Center Name/ID 

Join Over 950,000 Subscribers!
------------------------------

Stay up to date on how God is working through our ministry.

Thank you for subscribing

* 
* 
* 
* 

Follow Us

Ways to Give

Ways to Advocate

Quick Links

Contact Us

* Monday through Friday
* 7:00 a.m. to 5:30 p.m. (MT)

Follow Us

[Privacy Statement](https://www.compassion.com/privacy-policy.htm) [Conditions of Use](https://www.compassion.com/conditions-of-use.htm) [Disclosure Statement](https://www.compassion.com/about/disclosure-statement.htm) [Cookie Settings](javascript:OneTrust.ToggleInfoDisplay();) [Site Map](https://www.compassion.com/sitemap/sitemap.htm)

© 2024 Compassion International. All Rights Reserved.

Compassion International, Inc. is a registered 501(c)(3) nonprofit organization.  
Tax ID (EIN) 36-2423707

Compassion®, Compassion International®, Compassion Sunday®, the Compassion Logo and the FILL THE STADIUM Logo are registered trademarks of Compassion International, Inc.

All donations in the United States are tax deductible in full or part.

[Compassion strives to protect children from all forms of abuse.](https://www.compassion.com/how-we-work/commitment-child-protection.htm)

Javascript is required on this website, please Enable Javascript in your browser
